<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>red queen on Pointy&#39;s</title><link>https://pointyfar.github.io/pointybubl-demo/tags/red-queen/</link><description>Recent content in red queen on Pointy&#39;s</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 17:49:54 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pointyfar.github.io/pointybubl-demo/tags/red-queen/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CHAPTER X. Shaking</title><link>https://pointyfar.github.io/pointybubl-demo/looking-glass/chapter10/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 17:49:54 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://pointyfar.github.io/pointybubl-demo/looking-glass/chapter10/</guid><description>She took her off the table as she spoke, and shook her backwards and forwards with all her might.
The Red Queen made no resistance whatever; only her face grew very small, and her eyes got large and green: and still, as Alice went on shaking her, she kept on growing shorter&amp;ndash;and fatter&amp;ndash;and softer&amp;ndash;and rounder&amp;ndash;and&amp;ndash;</description></item><item><title>CHAPTER IX. Queen Alice</title><link>https://pointyfar.github.io/pointybubl-demo/looking-glass/chapter9/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 17:49:51 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://pointyfar.github.io/pointybubl-demo/looking-glass/chapter9/</guid><description>‘Well, this IS grand!’ said Alice. ‘I never expected I should be a Queen so soon&amp;ndash;and I’ll tell you what it is, your majesty,’ she went on in a severe tone (she was always rather fond of scolding herself), ‘it’ll never do for you to be lolling about on the grass like that! Queens have to be dignified, you know!’
So she got up and walked about&amp;ndash;rather stiffly just at first, as she was afraid that the crown might come off: but she comforted herself with the thought that there was nobody to see her, ‘and if I really am a Queen,’ she said as she sat down again, ‘I shall be able to manage it quite well in time.</description></item><item><title>CHAPTER II. The Garden of Live Flowers</title><link>https://pointyfar.github.io/pointybubl-demo/looking-glass/chapter2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 17:49:33 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://pointyfar.github.io/pointybubl-demo/looking-glass/chapter2/</guid><description>‘I should see the garden far better,’ said Alice to herself, ‘if I could get to the top of that hill: and here’s a path that leads straight to it&amp;ndash;at least, no, it doesn’t do that&amp;ndash;’ (after going a few yards along the path, and turning several sharp corners), ‘but I suppose it will at last. But how curiously it twists! It’s more like a corkscrew than a path! Well, THIS turn goes to the hill, I suppose&amp;ndash;no, it doesn’t!</description></item></channel></rss>