<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lewis Caroll on Pointy&#39;s</title>
    <link>https://pointyfar.github.io/authors/lewis-carroll/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lewis Caroll on Pointy&#39;s</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2018 16:28:44 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://pointyfar.github.io/authors/lewis-carroll/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER XII. Which Dreamed it?</title>
      <link>https://pointyfar.github.io/looking-glass/chapter12/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 17:59:21 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pointyfar.github.io/looking-glass/chapter12/</guid>
      <description>‘Your majesty shouldn’t purr so loud,’ Alice said, rubbing her eyes, and addressing the kitten, respectfully, yet with some severity. ‘You woke me out of oh! such a nice dream! And you’ve been along with me, Kitty&amp;ndash;all through the Looking-Glass world. Did you know it, dear?’
It is a very inconvenient habit of kittens (Alice had once made the remark) that, whatever you say to them, they ALWAYS purr. ‘If they would only purr for “yes” and mew for “no,” or any rule of that sort,’ she had said, ‘so that one could keep up a conversation!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER XI. Waking</title>
      <link>https://pointyfar.github.io/looking-glass/chapter11/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 17:59:18 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pointyfar.github.io/looking-glass/chapter11/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ndash;and it really WAS a kitten, after all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER X. Shaking</title>
      <link>https://pointyfar.github.io/looking-glass/chapter10/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 17:49:54 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pointyfar.github.io/looking-glass/chapter10/</guid>
      <description>She took her off the table as she spoke, and shook her backwards and forwards with all her might.
The Red Queen made no resistance whatever; only her face grew very small, and her eyes got large and green: and still, as Alice went on shaking her, she kept on growing shorter&amp;ndash;and fatter&amp;ndash;and softer&amp;ndash;and rounder&amp;ndash;and&amp;ndash;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER IX. Queen Alice</title>
      <link>https://pointyfar.github.io/looking-glass/chapter9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 17:49:51 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pointyfar.github.io/looking-glass/chapter9/</guid>
      <description>‘Well, this IS grand!’ said Alice. ‘I never expected I should be a Queen so soon&amp;ndash;and I’ll tell you what it is, your majesty,’ she went on in a severe tone (she was always rather fond of scolding herself), ‘it’ll never do for you to be lolling about on the grass like that! Queens have to be dignified, you know!’
So she got up and walked about&amp;ndash;rather stiffly just at first, as she was afraid that the crown might come off: but she comforted herself with the thought that there was nobody to see her, ‘and if I really am a Queen,’ she said as she sat down again, ‘I shall be able to manage it quite well in time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER VIII. ‘It’s my own Invention’</title>
      <link>https://pointyfar.github.io/looking-glass/chapter8/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 17:49:48 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pointyfar.github.io/looking-glass/chapter8/</guid>
      <description>After a while the noise seemed gradually to die away, till all was dead silence, and Alice lifted up her head in some alarm. There was no one to be seen, and her first thought was that she must have been dreaming about the Lion and the Unicorn and those queer Anglo-Saxon Messengers. However, there was the great dish still lying at her feet, on which she had tried to cut the plum-cake, ‘So I wasn’t dreaming, after all,’ she said to herself, ‘unless&amp;ndash;unless we’re all part of the same dream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER VII. The Lion and the Unicorn</title>
      <link>https://pointyfar.github.io/looking-glass/chapter7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 17:49:47 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pointyfar.github.io/looking-glass/chapter7/</guid>
      <description>The next moment soldiers came running through the wood, at first in twos and threes, then ten or twenty together, and at last in such crowds that they seemed to fill the whole forest. Alice got behind a tree, for fear of being run over, and watched them go by.
She thought that in all her life she had never seen soldiers so uncertain on their feet: they were always tripping over something or other, and whenever one went down, several more always fell over him, so that the ground was soon covered with little heaps of men.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER VI. Humpty Dumpty</title>
      <link>https://pointyfar.github.io/looking-glass/chapter6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 17:49:44 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pointyfar.github.io/looking-glass/chapter6/</guid>
      <description>However, the egg only got larger and larger, and more and more human: when she had come within a few yards of it, she saw that it had eyes and a nose and mouth; and when she had come close to it, she saw clearly that it was HUMPTY DUMPTY himself. ‘It can’t be anybody else!’ she said to herself. ‘I’m as certain of it, as if his name were written all over his face.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER V. Wool and Water</title>
      <link>https://pointyfar.github.io/looking-glass/chapter5/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 17:49:42 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pointyfar.github.io/looking-glass/chapter5/</guid>
      <description>She caught the shawl as she spoke, and looked about for the owner: in another moment the White Queen came running wildly through the wood, with both arms stretched out wide, as if she were flying, and Alice very civilly went to meet her with the shawl.
‘I’m very glad I happened to be in the way,’ Alice said, as she helped her to put on her shawl again.
The White Queen only looked at her in a helpless frightened sort of way, and kept repeating something in a whisper to herself that sounded like ‘bread-and-butter, bread-and-butter,’ and Alice felt that if there was to be any conversation at all, she must manage it herself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER IV. Tweedledum And Tweedledee</title>
      <link>https://pointyfar.github.io/looking-glass/chapter4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 17:49:40 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pointyfar.github.io/looking-glass/chapter4/</guid>
      <description>They were standing under a tree, each with an arm round the other’s neck, and Alice knew which was which in a moment, because one of them had ‘DUM’ embroidered on his collar, and the other ‘DEE.’ ‘I suppose they’ve each got “TWEEDLE” round at the back of the collar,’ she said to herself.
They stood so still that she quite forgot they were alive, and she was just looking round to see if the word “TWEEDLE” was written at the back of each collar, when she was startled by a voice coming from the one marked ‘DUM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER III. Looking-Glass Insects</title>
      <link>https://pointyfar.github.io/looking-glass/chapter3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 17:49:36 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pointyfar.github.io/looking-glass/chapter3/</guid>
      <description>Of course the first thing to do was to make a grand survey of the country she was going to travel through. ‘It’s something very like learning geography,’ thought Alice, as she stood on tiptoe in hopes of being able to see a little further. ‘Principal rivers&amp;ndash;there ARE none. Principal mountains&amp;ndash;I’m on the only one, but I don’t think it’s got any name. Principal towns&amp;ndash;why, what ARE those creatures, making honey down there?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER II. The Garden of Live Flowers</title>
      <link>https://pointyfar.github.io/looking-glass/chapter2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 17:49:33 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pointyfar.github.io/looking-glass/chapter2/</guid>
      <description>‘I should see the garden far better,’ said Alice to herself, ‘if I could get to the top of that hill: and here’s a path that leads straight to it&amp;ndash;at least, no, it doesn’t do that&amp;ndash;’ (after going a few yards along the path, and turning several sharp corners), ‘but I suppose it will at last. But how curiously it twists! It’s more like a corkscrew than a path! Well, THIS turn goes to the hill, I suppose&amp;ndash;no, it doesn’t!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CHAPTER I. Looking-Glass house</title>
      <link>https://pointyfar.github.io/looking-glass/chapter1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 17:49:25 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pointyfar.github.io/looking-glass/chapter1/</guid>
      <description>One thing was certain, that the WHITE kitten had had nothing to do with it:&amp;ndash;it was the black kitten’s fault entirely. For the white kitten had been having its face washed by the old cat for the last quarter of an hour (and bearing it pretty well, considering); so you see that it COULDN’T have had any hand in the mischief.
The way Dinah washed her children’s faces was this: first she held the poor thing down by its ear with one paw, and then with the other paw she rubbed its face all over, the wrong way, beginning at the nose: and just now, as I said, she was hard at work on the white kitten, which was lying quite still and trying to purr&amp;ndash;no doubt feeling that it was all meant for its good.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>